Guide to the Gail and Stephen Rudin slavery collection, 1728-1973.
Rudin (Gail and Stephen) Slavery Collection,
- Series IX: Miscellaneous Documents
  - Man receives permission to return his slave force to his plantation after assisting with the defenses of Atlanta, October 27, 1863; Location: Atlanta, GA Format: MDocS (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Rudin # S - 293
  - Pair of cancelled checks issued by New York City for Draft Riot damages, November 30, December 17, 1863; Format: Ptd DOCS (Box 6, Folder 13A)
    Rudin # S - 1041
  - Check issued by New York City in compensation for property damage during draft riots, December 10, 1863; Location: New York City Format: Ptd Docs (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Rudin # S - 734
  - Special Order #10 - Tax to be Levied on the Labor of all Southern Freedmen for the Support of the Sick and Dependent of their Race, December 29, 1863; Location: Vicksburg, Mississippi Format: MDocS (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Rudin # S - 518
  - South Carolina Slave Impressment: recouping loss of impressed slave, February 10, 1864 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Rudin # S - 52
  - CSA Certificate, plowman pictured, February 17, 1864 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    Rudin # S - 696
  - Andrews (White Man) is Appointed 2nd Lt of 36th Regiment of US Colored Infantry, February 29, 1864; Location: Department of Virginia, North Carolina Format: Ptd DOCS (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Rudin # S - 411
  - Death certificate for slave who was required to work on confederate earthworks around Charleston. Died in a "Negro hospital", May 1, 1864; Location: Charleston, South Carolina Format: MDocS (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Rudin # S - 760
  - Permit to Sell 100 Bales of Cotton, May 6, 1864; Location: Port of Little Rock, Arkansas Format: Ptd DOC (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Rudin # S - 576
  - Union "Oath of Allegiance" Broadside, September 22, 1864; Location: Norfolk, Virginia Format: Ptd BROADSIDE (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Rudin # S - 489
  - Free Black Civil War Pass to Move Four Bales of Cotton, November 15, 1864; Location: Natchez, Mississippi Format: MDocS (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Rudin # S - 420
  - Claim for Impressed Slave who died while working on Ft. Sumter, November, 1864; Location: South Carolina Format: MDocS (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Rudin # S - 151
    See also G. T. Beauregard letter regarding Fort Sumter in collection #6875.
  - An African American man offers to serve as a substitute soldier in the Union Army, November 26, 1864; Location: Camden County, New Jersey Format: Ptd Doc (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Rudin # S - 745
  - Confederate Printed Broadside, "Joint Resolutions" Regarding Impressments and the Schedule of Prices Fixed by the Confederate Commissioners, December 24, 1864; Location: Richmond, Virginia Format: Ptd Broadside (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Rudin # S - 527
  - "Negro" Passport, 1865; Location: Richmond, Virginia Format: Ptd Doc (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Rudin # S - 525
  - Civil War Form Signed by an Officer of the U.S. Colored Troops for Subsistence for Himself and Black Servant, January 31, 1865; Location: On the Field, Virginia Format: Ptd DocS (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Rudin # S - 480
  - Court Marshall of a Black Musician, March 15, 1865; Location: Helena, Arkansas Format: MDocS (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Rudin # S - 439
  - Enlistment bounty for slave soldier and receipt of payment, June, 1865; Location: Baltimore, Maryland Format: Ptd Docs (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Rudin # S - 639
  - Oath of Allegiance, June 3, 1865; Location: Virginia (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Rudin # S - 94
  - Labor contract with freedmen, July 8, 1865; Location: Marion County, Texas Format: Ptd Doc (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Rudin # S - 671
  - Paroled POW signs oath of allegiance, June 16, 1865; Location: Baton Rouge, Louisiana Format: Ptd Docs (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Rudin # S - 819
  - General Order #129 - Equal Treatment of Blacks, July 25, 1865; Location: Washington; Format: "Ptd DOC" (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Circular No. 13 - Freedman's Bureau Carves Up the Conquered South, August 16, 1865; Location: Washington, DC Format: MDocS (Box 17, Folder 12)
    Rudin # S - 310
  - Black Matron's Pay (Matron of a US Army Hospital), August 31, 1865; Location: (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Rudin # S - 49
  - Signed oath of loyalty for officers of the Missouri militia, signed by DL Woodson, September 11, 1865; Location: Audrain County, Missouri Format: Ptd Docs (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Rudin # S - 667
  - Oath of Allegiance, September 16, 1865; Location: County of Stanly Format: MDocS (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Rudin # S - 237
  - Agreement Between Former Masters and Slaves, October 9, 1865; Location: Abbeville District, South Carolina Format: MDocS (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Rudin # S - 295
  - Amnesty Oath: Ex-Confederate soldier swears to uphold the constitution with specific mention of slaves, October 10, 1865; Location: Florida Format: Ptd Docs (Box 6, Folder 33)
    Rudin # S - 802
  - Miller Contract and Farmland Contract Approved by The Freedmen Bureau, December 29, 1865; Location: Lumpkin County, Georgia Format: MDocS (Box 6, Folder 34)
    Rudin # S - 220
  - Post Civil War agreement between William Kinder and 29 Freedmen and Women, January 23, 1866; Location: Williamsburg District, South Carolina Format: DocS (Box 6, Folder 35)
    Rudin # S - 895
  - Document of DeFacto Slavery (Four Year-Old Boy), February 27, 1866 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    Rudin # S - 30
  - Freed Slave (George Washington) is discharged from Colored Troop., March 13, 1866; Location: Natchez, Mississippi Format: Ptd Doc (Box 6, Folder 36)
    Rudin # S - 654
  - Military pay voucher for General Sickles and his four servants, April 2, 1866; Location: Charleston, South Carolina Format: Ptd Doc (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Rudin # S - 850
  - Louisiana Amnesty Oath, May 17, 1866 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    Rudin # S - 14
  - Receipt for Making Four Coffins for Negroes Who Died on the Plantation, May 17, 1866; Location: Anson County, North Carolina Format: MDocS (Box 6, Folder 38)
    Rudin # S - 408
  - A Marriage License and Marriage Certificate for a Slave Couple, December 25-26, 1867; Location: Gallation County, Kentucky Format: Ptd Doc (Box 6, Folder 39)
    Rudin # S - 481
  - Motion to Throw Black Legislators Out of Georgia Legislature, ca. 1868; Location: Milledgeville, Georgia Format: Partial AMS (Box 6, Folder 40)
    Rudin # S - 454
  - Reconstruction Contract with ex-slaves for labor, 1868; Location:North Carolina (Box 6, Folder 41)
    Rudin # S - 53
  - Home for Destitute Colored Children- indenture to last 12 years for a young black man to work, July 4, 1868; Location: Maylandville, Pennsylvania Format: Ptd Doc (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Rudin # S -932
  - KKK Blocks Freed Slaves from Voting in Georgia, July 7, 1868; Location: Atlanta, Georgia Format: ALS (Box 6, Folder 42)
    Rudin # S - 479
  - Democratic National Union "No Negro Suffrage" Ballot, 1869; Location: Ohio Format: Ptd DOC (Box 6, Folder 43)
    Rudin # S - 437
  - Navy discharge record of African American sailor, George Bailey, from the US Ship Vandalia, February 26, 1869; Format: Ptd Docs (Box 6, Folder 44)
    Rudin # S - 945
  - Contract whereby Georgia Leases African American Prisoners for Railroad Construction in an effort to circumvent the abolition of Slavery., May 20, 1869; Location: Georgia Format: MDocS (Box 6, Folder 45)
    Rudin # S - 588
  - Oath of Allegiance, June 26, 1869; Location: West Virginia Format: Ptd Doc (Box 6, Folder 46)
    Rudin # S - 397
  - $1000 bond- Cotton wagon at pier, 1870; Location: New Orleans, Louisiana Format: Bond (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Rudin # S - 693
  - Concert broadside for "Donavin's Original Tennesseeans Slave Cabin Singers", 1870s; Location: Catasauqua, Pennsylvania Format: Broadside (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Rudin # S - 983
  - Special Orders Cancel "Wrongful Apprenticeships" - By Order of Major General Terry, May 5, 1870; Location: Atlanta, GA Format: Ptd Doc (Box 6, Folder 47)
    Rudin # S - 248
  - Special Orders Cancel "Wrongful Apprenticeships" - By Order of Major General Terry, May 30, 1870; Location: Atlanta, Georgia Format: Ptd Doc (Box 6, Folder 48)
    Rudin # S - 249
  - Henry Farrow, the injustice of poll taxes, ca. 1872; Location: Richmond, Virginia Format: Broadside (Folder 5)
    Rudin # S - 985
  - $500 bond, men hauling cotton, 1874; Location: Mississippi Format: Bond (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Rudin # S - 730
  - Buffalo soldier named George Washington is discharged and receives his final pay, September 22, 1874; Location: Washington, DC Format: Ptd Doc (Box 6, Folder 49)
    Rudin # S - 996
  - Pair of dated discharge documents for a "Buffalo Soldier" named Thomas Grant, February 7 and 28, 1875; Format: Ptd Docs (Box 6, Folder 50)
    Rudin # S - 632
  - Quote signed "Peace if possible, Justice at any rate", 1877; Format: AQS (Box 6, Folder 51)
    Rudin # S - 435
  - Petition for Lenience for a Negro Convicted of Stealing, October 6, 1886; Location: Farmsville, South Carolina Format: MDocS (Box 6, Folder 52)
    Rudin # S - 406
  - Color Chart of "White and Colored Population of the Southern States", Rand Mcnally, 1890; Location: Chicago, Illinois (Box 26, Folder 9)
    Rudin # S - 999
  - 1-Star "Liberia" Flag, ca. 1890s; Location: Country of Liberia Format: FLAG (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Rudin # S - 585
  - $500 Constitutional bond, 1892; Location: New Orleans, Louisiana Format: Bond (Box 17, Folder 14)
    Rudin # S - 694
  - 'Little JL Washington, the Walking Bible Prodigy' broadside with image, August 22, 1896; Location: Yorktown Baptist Church Format: Broadside (Folder 2)
    Rudin # S - 842
  - $1000 Mortgage bond, 1901; Location: Columbia, Louisiana Format: Bond (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Rudin # S - 697
  - Three Sharecroppers' contracts signed with an "X" by each tenant farmer, 1907-1909; Location: Tunica, Mississippi Format: Ptd DocS (Box 6, Folder 53)
    Rudin # S - 780
  - Pinkerton's National Detective Agency Reward Poster for a Black Man, August 12, 1918; Location: Buchanan County, Missouri Format: Ptd Poster (Box 6, Folder 54)
    Rudin # S - 568
  - Facsimile account book recording expenses to assist fugitive slaves during the 1850s and 1860s, 1924; Location: Boston, Massachusetts Format: Account book (Box 6, Folder 55)
    Rudin # S - 968
- Series VIII: Music
  - "Kingdom Coming", Location: Root and Cady Publishers, Chicago Format: Ptd song sheet (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Rudin # S - 534
  - Collection of 91 Song sheets, Location: Philadelphia Format: Ptd song sheet (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Rudin # S - 532
  - Colored Regiments Recruiting Broadside "A Contraband Song", Format: Ptd song sheet (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Rudin # S - 474
  - Civil War colored songsheets: "Darkey Conscript", "Kitty Wells", Format: Ptd Sheet music (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Rudin # S - 1006
  - Freedom song of the Mississippi Contrabands, "A Contraband Song, Old Shady", Format: Ptd Sheet music (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Rudin # S - 835
  - "Kingdom Coming" hand colored, Format: Ptd Sheet music (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Rudin # S - 763
  - Six civil war songs by Charles Magnus, each hand colored and bound in an accordion folding pamphlet, Format: Song Sheets (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Rudin # S - 610
  - "I Long For My Home in Kentuck", Location: Metzler and Co, London Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Rudin # S - 1031L
  - "Minstrel's Return from the War", Location: Mew York Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Rudin # S - 1031Q
  - "The Coal Black Rose", 1820s; Location: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Rudin # S - 953
  - Minstrel tale of a river dweller Gumbo Chaff, 1830s; Location: Baltimore, Maryland Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Rudin # S - 952
  - "To the West! To the West! To the Land of the Free!", ca. 1840; Format: Song sheet (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Rudin # S - 629
  - "Nelly Was a Lady", 1840; Location: Firth, Pond and Co., New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Rudin # S - 1031M
  - "Deacon Snowball's Negro Melodies", 1843; Format: Song Book (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Rudin # S - 1011
  - "The Slave Chase" - Composed by Henry Russell, ca. 1845; Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Rudin # S - 348
  - Ethiopian Serenaders Minstrel Sheet Music - "Rosa Lee", 1847; Location: New York - William Hall and Son Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Rudin # S - 419
  - "Uncle Ned" by Stephen Foster, ca. 1850s; Location: London, England Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Rudin # S - 960
  - "Massa's in De Cold Ground", ca. 1850; Format: Sheet music (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Rudin # S - 958
  - "Uncle True Songster", ca. 1850; Format: Song Book (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Rudin # S - 616
  - "Negro Melodies of the Day", 1850; Format: Song Book (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Rudin # S - 613
  - Abolitionist's Song "The Slave's Dream", ca. 1850; Location: B. Leverett Emerson Boston, MA Format: Ptd Broadside (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Rudin # S - 446
  - "Camptown Races," Published by Oliver Ditson & Co., 1850; Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Rudin # S - 159
  - "Old Uncle Ned Songster", ca. 1851-1860; Format: Songbook (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Rudin # S - 615
  - "White Serenaders' Song Book, No. 4", "Christy's Plantation Melodies, No. 2", 1851-1853; Format: Songbooks (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Rudin # S - 989
  - "Old Folks at Home", 1851; Location: Fifth Pond and Co, NY Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Rudin # S - 1031J
  - "Darkies Our Master's Gone to Town," Published by E. H. Wade, 1851; Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Rudin # S - 162
  - "Aolean Melodies" and "Poor Mary Cook," Published by E. H. Wade, 1851; Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Rudin # S - 160
  - "Poor Old Slave," Published by G. P. Reed & Co., 1851; Location: Boston, MA Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Rudin # S - 155, S - 1030
  - "Little Eva" Abolitionist Song - Dedicated to Harriet Beecher Stowe, 1852; Location: Boston - Jewett and Co. Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Rudin # S - 394
  - "Rosa Lane", 1852; Location: Edward Walker, Philadelphia PA Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Rudin # S - 1031H
  - "Little Eva-Uncle Tom's Guardian Angel", "Uncle Tom's Glimpse of Glory", "Uncle Tom's Religion", ca. 1852; Location: Boston, Massachusetts Format: Ptd Song Sheet (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Rudin # S - 271
  - Sheet Music: "I am Going There" or "The Death of Little Eva," Published by Oliver Ditson, 1852 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Rudin # S - 165
  - "Song of Eva - In Uncle Tom's Cabin", 1852; Location: Boston, Massachusetts Format: Sheet music (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Rudin # S - 822
  - "Katy Darling", 1852; Location: New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Rudin # S - 1031W
  - "Topsy's Song" with "Eva and Topsy" illustration, 1852; Location: London, England Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Rudin # S - 823
  - "Massa's in De Cold Ground", 1852; Location: Firth, Pond and Co., New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Rudin # S - 1031O
  - "Katy's Cry 'Come and Buy My Hot Corn'", 1853; Location: New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Rudin # S - 1031P
  - "Sweet Mississippi", 1853; Location: Sep. Winner, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Rudin # S - 1031R
  - "Kitty Crow," Published by C. C. Clapp & Co., 1853; Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Rudin # S - 154
  - "My Old Kentucky Home, Good Night," Published by Firth, Pond & Co., 1853; Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 11)
    Rudin # S - 163
  - "Meet me in Heaven" or the "Night Funeral of a Slave", 1854; Location: Boston, Massachusetts Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Rudin # S - 679
  - "Christy's Panorama Songster" (Minstrel Songster), ca. 1855; Location: William H. Murray New York Format: Songbook (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Rudin # S - 515
  - "Bryant's Programme and Songs", "Christy's Plantation Melodies", 1856, 1860; Format: Song sheets (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Rudin # S - 1007
  - "Bryants Essence of Old Virginny", 1859; Format: Song Book (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Rudin # S - 655
  - "Henry De Marsan's New Comic and Sentimental Singer's Journal" - "Containing all the most Popular Songs of the Day", ca. 1860; Location: 60 Chatham Street, New York Format: Ptd song sheet (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Rudin # S - 566
  - Hand colored, "Back and the Belly", 1860; Format: Song sheet (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Rudin # S - 627
  - "Joe Buggin's Wedding", ca. 1860; Format: Song sheet (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Rudin # S - 631
  - "Fred Wilson's Clog Dances", 1860; Location: Boston, Massachusetts Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Rudin # S - 806
  - Sheet Music, "Dixie's Land, with Brilliant Variations" - Early variant printing of "I Wish I Was In Dixie Land", 1860; Location: New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 12)
    Rudin # S - 591
  - Tom The Blind Negro Boy Pianist - Only 10 Years Old - Sheet Music - "Oliver Gallop", ca. 1860s; Location: New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Rudin # S - 428
  - "I Wish I Was in Dixie's Land," Published by Oliver Ditson & Co., 1860; Location: Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Rudin # S - 157
  - "Kittie Wells", 1861; Location: ST Gordon, New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Rudin # S - 1031A
  - Civil War Sheet Music: The "Contraband Schottische", 1861; Location: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 15)
    Rudin # S - 364
  - "The Contraband Schottisch," Published by Lee and Walker, 1861; Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 16)
    Rudin # S - 166
  - "Raw Recruits or Abraham's Daughter" Song Book - Hand-Colored Cover Illustration, 1861; Location: New York Format: Song Book (Box 19, Folder 17)
    Rudin # S - 287
  - Emancipation Hymn "Let the Men Go", October 14, 1861; Location: New York, NY Format: Ptd Song sheet (Box 7, Folder 21)
    Rudin # S - 387
  - "War Songs, for Anniversaries and Gatherings of Soldiers", 1861-1865; Format: Music Book (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Rudin # S - 803
  - "Dixie's Land", ca. 1861; Format: Song sheet (Box 7, Folder 23)
    Rudin # S - 1020
  - "De Day ob Liberty's comin", 1862; Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 17)
    Rudin # S - 1039A
  - "The Negro Emancipation Song", 1862; Location: Chicago, Illinois Format: Song sheet (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Rudin # S - 751
  - "Young Folks at Home", 1862; Location: Gould and Berry, New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Rudin # S - 1031B
  - "Song of the Negro Boatmen," Published by Root and Cady, 1862; Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Rudin # S - 161
  - "Fifty Cents a Day", ca. 1863; Format: Song sheet (Box 7, Folder 24)
    Rudin # S - 641
  - "Wake Nicodemus!", ca. 1863; Format: Song sheet (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Rudin # S - 1027
  - "New Orleans Minstrels", "Sweet Singer", "Last Words", 1863-1880; Format: Song books (Box 36)
    Rudin # S - 1012
  - "Wake Nicodemus"- verse and music, 1864; Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 17)
    Rudin # S - 1039B
  - "Wake Nicodemus," Published by Root and Cady. Two copies, 1864; Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Rudin # S - 156, S - 1031I
  - "Patriotic Songs: Your Sons and Your Money on Your Country's Altar", 1865; Format: Ptd Broadsheet (Box 26, Folder 9)
    Rudin # S - 849
  - "Times hab badly change ole massa now", 1866; Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 17)
    Rudin # S - 1039C
  - "Plantation Melodies: and "The Gum Tree Canoe," Published by Geo. P. Reed, 1867; Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 20)
    Rudin # S - 164
  - "Christy's New Songster and Black Joker", 1868; Location: Dick and Fitzgerald Publishers, New York Format: Ptd Song book (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Rudin # S - 565
  - "Shew Fly", "Uncle Josh's Huskin Dance", 1869; 1898; Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Rudin # S - 791
  - "New and Original Song and Dance: Love Among the Roses", 1869; Location: New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Rudin # S - 805
  - "Old Uncle Ben, The Colored Refugee", 1869; Location: New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Rudin # S - 979
  - Concert Program - "Songs, Sketch of the Life, of Blind Tom the Marvelous Musical Prodigy, The Negro Boy Pianist", ca. 1870; Location: New York Format: Ptd Program (Box 7, Folder 27)
    Rudin # S - 484
  - "Contraband Children," Published by C. H. Ditson & Co., 1872; Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Rudin # S - 158
  - "Skidmore Guard", a humorous song about colored troops, 1875; Format: Song sheet (Box 7, Folder 27A)
    Rudin # S - 1033
  - "The Old Log Cabin in the Lane", 1875; Location: Brooklyn, New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Rudin # S - 980
  - "Walking for Dat Cake", 1877; Location: New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Rudin # S - 965
  - Slavery Songbook by A. J. Fisher, 1877; Format: Ptd Sheet music (Box 7, Folder 28)
    Rudin # S - 87
  - "The Camptown Races", 1882; Location: New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Rudin # S - 862
  - "Minstrel Songs Old and New", 1882; Location: Boston, Massachusetts Format: Song Book (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Rudin # S - 976
  - Appearance of the Catawampus Negro Minstrels, New Hampshire, 1884; Format: Music broadside (Box 7, Folder 29)
    Rudin # S - 866
  - "Old Black Joe", 1885; Location: New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Rudin # S - 1031K
  - Broadside for Grand Sacred Concert by the Tennessee Jubilee Singers, and African American Singing Group, Format: Broadside (Folder 2)
    Rudin # S - 1035
  - "Good Bye my Honey I'm Gone", 1888; Location: National Music, Chicago Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Rudin # S - 1031N
  - "Happy Darkies" (Two Copies - one 8 pages and one 4 pages), 1892; Location: "London and New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Rudin # S - 367
  - Program for the "Black Patti Troubadours", New York, 1898; Format: Music Program (Box 7, Folder 30)
    Rudin # S - 986
  - "At a Darktown Cake Walk", 1899; Location: New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Rudin # S - 1031U
  - "The Cotton Pickers", "African Quadrilles, Negro Melodies", 1899; 1844; Location: New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Rudin # S - 677
  - "Songs of the Confederacy and Plantation Melodies" - Contains Twenty Songs, 1901; Location: Cincinatti, Ohio Format: Ptd song book (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Rudin # S - 294
  - "Evah Dahkey is a King", two copies, 1902; Location: Chicago, IL Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Rudin # S - 1031E
  - "I Am de Leadin' Lady ob de Town", 1902; Location: Fred King Music, Chicago, IL Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Rudin # S - 1031D
  - "By The Watermelon Vine Lindy Lou", 1904; Location: Boston, Massachusetts Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Rudin # S - 1031V
  - "There's A Dark Man Coming With a Bundle", 1904; Location: New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Rudin # S - 1031T
  - "When Angelina Johnson Comes A-swingin Down De Line", 1905; Location: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Rudin # S - 1031S
  - "Plantation Melodies and Spiritual Songs", ca. 1910s; Format: Song Book (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Rudin # S - 967
  - "Twenty-Four Negro Melodies", 1905; Location:Boston, Massachusetts Format: Song Book (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Rudin # S - 972
  - "If Every Star was a Little Pickaninny", 1912; Location: Leo. Feist, New York Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Rudin # S - 1031C
  - "Somebody's Done Me Wrong"- "The Best Coon Shout Ever Written", 1918; Location: Jos. W. Stern Co, NY Format: Sheet Music (Box 20, Folder 12)
    Rudin # S - 1031G
- Series XI: Newspapers
  - "London Gazette" discussing a slave mutiny, September 13, 1675; Location: London, England (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Rudin # S - 777
  - "Pennsylvania Packet" offering rewards for runaway slave, August 31, 1772; Location: Pennsylvania (Box 22, Folder 5)
    Rudin # S - 605A